SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
Lumi.
I want to work in this place.
NORTHWESTERN CULTURAL TOURISM
DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, BUSINESS DIVISION ONE
Northwestern China?
That's so far away from here.
And the project will run
for 14 months, not 14 days.
I know. But I have made up my mind.
Tracy told me that
while I passed all the requirements,
I still needed a bit more.
I have never managed
any S+ projects of highly importance.
This is a great opportunity.
It's all I need now.
Same here.
You have not given up yet?
The boy is mine.
He saved my life.
It's only right for me to marry him.
What? When did he save your life?
My ex harassed me a while ago.
We almost got physical.
And he suddenly appeared to save me.
He fought two enemies alone,
and he did not lose.
So manly. He looks like a nerd,
but how can he be
so handsome when he fights?
His abs. His posture. I was like…
Did he look at me?
He did.
ANOTHER LEAP OF FAITH
Come in.
Luke.
Take a seat.
I would like to apply
to join the Northwestern
Cultural Tourism
Development Project team next month.
That is a tough subject.
You only return here
for two days per month.
Still, I want to join.
Why?
Because I believe we all have a value
and a place we need to be.
Where there is a risk,
there is an opportunity too.
I'm still young. I want to take the risk.
I'm also aware
that given my average skills,
I won't be able to pick up an S+ project
unless it is very far away.
Shang Zhitao, you won't admit this,
but you are selling yourself short.
You want to tread off the beaten path
and hope it may lead to success.
But someone has to make
the path first, right?
No one wants to make this path, but I do.
Luke. Can you approve it?
This is also on my wishlist.
I have a wishlist.
I really want the expert title.
Fine.
As you wish.
Okay.
Thanks.
What about Luke then?
I haven't thought about it.
When push comes to shove,
I'll bring him with me.
You can let him live with me.
He knows my place well anyway.
I wouldn't want to trouble you,
But thanks.
So…
You broke up?
I don't know.
I guess so.
He rejected me,
but I wasn't embarrassed or anything.
And I do not resent him either.
Now I've become an emotionless workaholic.
Perhaps you didn't love him that much.
Or perhaps
a true heartbreak is always silent.
Or perhaps…
Or perhaps we have never fallen in love.
Even though we were in a relationship,
it was never real.
I don't think it's gastric.
I just feel a bit bloated.
Wait. Are you still with that girl?
Did you use protection?
What are you saying?
Just be frank.
All right then.
Did you contract any STDs?
I'm about to be as chaste as a monk.
SHANG ZHITAO
Yes?
Is Luke's rabies
vaccine certificate with you?
Yes. I have it.
But I'm sick now. I can't go out.
Why don't you drop by my place?
Get me some medicine.
I'll send the brand to you.
Luke.
Are you okay?
Where does it hurt? You're in pain.
Are you sure the medicine will help?
Let's go to the hospital.
I don't like hospitals.
It hurts so much.
I can't find the vaccine certificate.
It's too late for you to get one anyway.
I don't like to owe anyone a favor.
Given that you brought medicine for me,
fine,
I'll take care of Luke for you.
You… You're sick,
And I've already checked your schedule.
You have a business trip next week.
Your flatmates also have business trips.
Besides, my neighborhood
has a dedicated dog sitter.
NORTHWESTERN CHINA
Sun Yuanzhu.
You have lost a lot of weight.
Is the food here that bad?
No, it's good.
I have been busy, that's all.
Then, I shouldn't have
asked you to pick me up.
No way.
Tao. I'm so happy that you're here.
Following your footsteps,
I have come here to achieve my ambition.
I, Ms. Shang Zhitao,
will be working with the local councils
as the project director of Lime.
I will combine the local culture
and digital technology
to develop a new cultural tourism.
What do you think? Is that impressive?
Ms. Shang Zhitao,
you have become a bigwig.
Yes.
May your project
become a huge success soon.
May your self-driving car
go on the street soon.
Okay.
Sun Yuanzhu. This is such
a special mountain range.
It's the spine of a dragon.
A dragon spine?
When I asked
to take on this distant project,
some said it was beyond my capability.
Some said I was trying
too hard to impress.
But I know very well
that when I look down,
it is to make sure
I am walking the right path.
I'm so glad I'm here.
NORTHWESTERN CHINA LAND LAW DRAFT
SECTION EIGHT
PROPERTY OWNERSHIP RESOLUTION
I used to think working
was drinking with the right person
at a business dinner.
But now I learned
that the real battle
takes place where no one is around.
THREE MONTHS LATER
It represents our ideal.
- Our idea…
- Flora.
Mr. Luan has arrived. Come.
Okay.
- Flora.
- Lumi.
I've missed you.
Allow me to introduce.
This is Flora, our project director
in Northwestern China.
Flora. Our new colleague.
Yilia.
Flora. We finally meet.
People have been
praising you at the office.
I can't wait to learn from you.
Likewise.
It's about time. Come in.
She's an elite who joined our division
all the way
from the headquarters in the US.
She bought her way in.
Is this project that important?
Even a bigwig like her is here.
Of course, you have
an influential figure backing you up.
Luke's presence is the greatest privilege
you can have.
And I'm here too.
Come.
We like dragons. We deify dragons.
Dragons are like our ideals.
Our idea should incorporate
this kind of ideal.
Instead of focusing on the landscape,
we should highlight
the generations that live here.
There are sculptures.
There is cultural heritage.
So what exactly is Northwestern China?
NORTHWESTERN CULTURAL TOURISM
TARGET AUDIENCES
WELLNESS SEEKERS & FAMILY TRAVELERS
TRENDY YOUTH & NICHE EXPLORERS
PRIMARY PALETTE & ITS IMPACT
That's all for my presentation.
Thank you for listening.
Please proceed to the lounge next to us.
We have prepared food and refreshments.
I have taught Flora well.
She made me proud.
She's so good.
She recognizes, values,
and manages talents very well.
She can do everything.
Flora is indeed exceptional in Lime.
She started from a humble background.
She has a clear goal
and works hard.
Her amicability is also
one of a kind in Lime.
Many colleagues remarked
that her passion and honesty
were exemplary attributes.
You're a smooth-talker today.
Go eat first.
I'll talk to Flora for a while.
Come. Let's eat.
NORTHWESTERN CULTURAL TOURISM
CONFERENCE HALL, BREAK ROOM
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Stop moving around. Okay?
Sit properly.
You'll be fine soon.
Am I going to die here?
What are you on about?
This is a good hospital.
Besides, I'm here.
Are you thirsty?
The doctor said
you shouldn't drink soda anymore.
Once we're back, I'll throw away
your cola and soda.
Are you hungry?
It's just a kidney stone.
I'm fine.
Just a kidney stone?
You're the one suffering here.
Does it not hurt anymore?
Why are you smiling?
Lie down.
Don't tell Lumi and the rest.
Just tell them I went back to Beijing.
You won't stay at the hotel?
No. I'm staying with you.
I need a carer.
Yes.
It's not out yet.
I had an X-ray yesterday.
The doctor said it was moving out.
It'll come out if I raise
my calves or climb stairs more often.
Don't worry.
Someone is looking after me.
Who, you asked?
My girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
Can I speak to her?
I need to talk to her
about your condition.
Or maybe I should fly
to Northwestern China and drag you back?
You want to speak to my girlfriend?
Okay.
It's my mom.
She thinks I have a terminal illness.
Hi, Dr. Liang.
Hi.
Miss, how should I address you?
Just call me Flora.
Flora.
I just want to know
about Luan Nian's condition.
Is it true that he has a kidney stone?
Yes, he has a kidney stone.
Don't worry about him.
Luke has already told you
what he needed to do.
I'll take him
to get his X-ray done in a few days.
So don't worry about it.
Okay.
Flora. I know Luan Nian has a bad temper
and he can be quite weird.
- But don't--
- Anyway,
as you already know, I'm not dead.
I'm hanging up now.
Make sure to take your medicine.
I have to work now.
When are you coming back?
As soon as possible.
Why are you lying on the couch?
You're back.
The mattress is too firm.
The comforter is not soft enough.
And it's too thick.
The pillow is too low.
Are you a princess or what?
You know what?
I'll get you a room in a hotel.
But you won't stay
in the same hotel as Lumi.
Is that okay?
No.
I just feel quite weak.
It hurts everywhere.
I'll just rest in the room. I'll lie down.
Maybe you should return to Beijing.
They have big hospitals there.
You won't have to wait as long.
I can't go back.
Even getting out of bed
takes a lot of effort.
I need time to recover.
I bought a free-range chicken.
Should I cook it for you?
Are you sure I won't be poisoned?
I can assure you
that it will be cooked thoroughly.
You will do it an injustice
if it's not delicious enough.
Let me cook.
You… Aren't you sick?
I can hang in there.
Come. Drink some soup.
Try it.
I can do this myself.
Just drink it.
What do you think?
It's good.
I'll give you a shopping list tomorrow.
Let's furnish the kitchen.
You know I don't cook here.
I can when I'm here.
How long are you staying here?
Until I recover.
Does it still hurt?
Occasionally.
After you eat, do some calf raises.
So?
How is my performance as a househusband?
Have you peed your kidney stone out?
I don't know.
But it doesn't hurt as much anymore.
Then, return to Beijing tomorrow.
I have taken a long leave.
Shang Zhitao.
You told me last time
that you were young,
so you wanted to take the risk.
Let's take another leap of faith.
I don't want to take the old path.
We are not doing that.
I'll come with you.
You can take me anywhere you want.
Shang Zhitao.
Luke has missed you a lot.
Whenever we do a video call,
Luke just rushes to me
whenever he hears you.
He's more honest than I am.
So, let me be honest with you.
After we broke up,
I felt awful.
It's as if I've lost
something precious to me.
I'm not good with words.
But I know I miss you.
I want to see you.
I want to take a leap of faith with you.
I want to see
if I can make it work between us.
I have thought about our future.
Can we start over again?
Tao.
Tell me. Do you not miss me?
You're so annoying.
I have missed you so much.
Shang Zhitao.
Come back to Beijing with me.
Come.
In what capacity
are you talking to me right now?
If you're speaking as my boyfriend,
I'll turn you down
because I like this project a lot.
I want to see it through,
and I hope you'll respect my choice.
If you're speaking as my boss,
then I'll come back.
Because you're my boss.
But I think it's a shame.
I don't know
if I'll ever have
a similar opportunity again in the future.
This is the only shot
that will most likely change my life.
Let's travel together.
Where to?
We'll bring the dog with us
and go wherever we want.
Where are we going next?
To Tibet, China.
Tibet, China?
What if I have altitude sickness?
We have oxygen bottles.
If I have altitude sickness,
will you look after me?
If you have altitude sickness,
I'll sell you off.
- It's dangerous.
- Come here.
Why are you staring at me?
You are so gentle today.
Have I ever hit you?
No.
I just wish you could be
this gentle with me more often.
So you like someone who's soft.
Luan Nian.
Do you know?
I think you should know this.
What?
I love to travel with you.
That's all?
Anything you want to add?
Luan Nian.
I love every path you take.
I love to go on an adventure with you.
I love the landscape on this journey.
Because we're doing it together.
MOM
- It's my mom.
- Pick it up.
Mom.
Why didn't you go on the trip
with Song Qiuhan and the rest?
I changed my mind. I have a road trip now.
A road trip?
With Flora?
You sure have a good memory.
I'm driving. I'll call you back
- when we take a break in the city.
- No need.
You're having fun right now.
No need to call me.
Just text me to tell me you're safe.
Flora.
Yes, Dr. Liang?
Luan Nian has a bad temper.
And he can be quite weird.
Thank you for putting up with him.
But don't take it lying down.
- If he does something wrong, you--
- Anyway.
I have a good temper. And I am not weird.
Bye.
Not weird, you said?
I think our son is in love.
And I think he really loves her.
It's just a trip. How is it real?
He was with Zang Yao for a decade.
Did he fall in love with her?
Honestly,
businessmen like you
only know how to do business.
Has he ever gone out with Zang Yao alone?
Also,
Luan Nian even admitted
that she was his girlfriend.
Has he ever done that?
You are just too eager
to be a grandmother.
Listen.
Don't be too eager.
Don't get your hopes up
because Luan Nian
has always been like this.
- He will mess things up.
- And he got that from you.
If only he were more like me.
Do you want to take photos?
You can pick your costumes inside.
Let me see.
Luan Nian. Do you like the photos here?
I do.
But I won't take them.
Sir.
Do you… Do you have a model here?
A male model
to take a couple of photos with me.
Yes.
You just have to pay extra.
Let me show you.
Young Tibetan men.
- Really?
- They are very handsome.
I want a handsome one
- to take photos, like--
- Shang Zhitao.
Which one do you want?
You pick one first.
Okay. Great.
Stay.
Hold it higher.
Yes! Great. This is good.
Two more single photos.
Your husband can join now.
- Stand here?
- Yes.
Stand closer to your wife.
Yes. Hug your wife.
Yes.
Don't be so stiff, you two.
Just relax.
Too stiff. Aren't you always
soft and relaxed?
Wonderful. Good.
Closer. Yes!
Good. Let's pick your photos here.
Come here already.
So gentle.
Is this the Luan Nian I know?
It feels like
we're dating for real this time.
Eat now, Luke.
He's so fat now. Stop feeding him.
Drink some water.
Thanks.
I appreciate that you never
threw tantrums at me.
You didn't leave me behind on the streets.
Congratulations.
You have become someone I trust.
- That's my honor.
- Of course.
- Mom.
- How is Tibet, China?
I love it here.
I eat well. I sleep well.
The scenery here is beautiful.
Luke is happy too.
Who are you traveling with?
Your boyfriend?
Yes. My boyfriend.
When did this happen?
- Who is he?
- Yes. Who?
How is his family?
How are his parents?
Is he kind?
Hi, Mrs. Shang. I am Luan Nian.
Hi. We are on the phone
together with Tao's dad.
- You are Mr. Luan, right?
- Give me that.
Yes, Mrs. Shang.
Tao and I have been dating for six years.
My family is okay.
- My annual income is--
- Enough.
Mom. I…
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
He hasn't even finished.
Why are you scared?
Too ashamed to tell anyone?
No.
I just…
Yes?
Luan Nian.
What?
Luke is here.
And you have altitude sickness. Be nice.
I think I'm fine.
I don't have altitude sickness.
Right.
Smooth your breathing first.
If something happens to you,
I'll have to collect your body.
Then, can we talk?
About what?
Let's talk
about the first time we met.
The first time we met?
In the office?
No.
You don't remember?
Where was it then?
In the hall.
I was like, how could someone
be this handsome?
You're the most handsome man I've met.
Your turn now.
Tell me.
When I first met you, I was thinking,
how could someone be this dumb?
Like a big dummy.
I'm tired now.
- Mad?
- No.
I'm just sleepy.
Shang Zhitao.
Should we catch the aurora next year?
I'll go
wherever you go.
This year is a good year.
I love this photo.
This one too.
This one is good.
You're a good photographer.
Thank you.
I want all of them.
We'll take everything then.
How much more should we pay?
No need to pay extra.
Can I hang one in my shop?
Then, you'll have to pay us.
Pick one
and hang it
at the most visible place in the shop.
Process it with the best film.
Once you're done, I'll inspect it.
Sure. No problem.
I'll give you the original film.
After I process it,
you can pick two as your wedding photos.
It'll last for many years.
The Tibetans use this
for their wedding photos.
I highly doubt I can get
good photos like this again.
Of course.
I'll count on you
to process the films, then.
Sure. Don't worry.
Luan Nian.